翻译 李SIR
翻译 阿蘅 somehacker
翻译 天意 Silmar
翻译 草草
时间轴 Imok
时间轴 大喷子
后期&特效  铭哥骑白马
校对&总监 天意
大西洋
帝国
『第四季 第十一集』
前情提要
你是怀特先生的孩子
You are Mr. White's child?
你快要结婚了对吧
And you are to be married, are you not?
本来是今天下午三点
Not as of 3:00 this afternoon.
为什么总要女儿们受罪
Why must it be the daughters who suffer?
照你说的做
What you told me.
无论如何  不能相信白人
Never trust no buckras, no matter what.
也别相信黑人
No browns neither.
你都说对了
You was right on both counts.
你地窖里有个臭鼬
There's a skunk in your cellar.
一个只有我了解的人
A certain individual I am uniquely qualified to provide.
告诉我是谁  米恩斯
Tell me a name, Means.
乔·马赫里亚  迈耶·兰斯基  卢西亚诺
Joe Masseria, Meyer Lansky, Luciano--
查理  还有佛罗里达的那个人
Charlie and the one in Florida.
我要让他们在一个屋里  伊莱
I need them all in a room, Eli,
跨越州线来计划共谋
making plans to operate in collusion across state lines.
那个买保险的肯定有你的电话
That insurance salesman sure had your number.
真正的蓝眼娃娃脸
Real blue-eyed baby face.
他只想把最贵的卖给你
All he wants to do is sell you the most expensive
琼  你能不能给我闭嘴
June, just shut your goddamn trap for once.
行吗
Okay?
死在这里的不是我儿子
It wasn't my son who died here.
是个无辜的男孩
It was an innocent boy.
他的名字叫罗杰
His name was Roger.
听到了吗
You get that?
听到了
I did.
我是平克顿私人侦探所的
I'm with the Pinkerton Detective Agency.
这些人是我的助手
These men are my associates
也是你供认一级谋杀罪的证人
and a witness your confession to first-degree murder.
我知道你喜欢放松
I know you like to relax.
我早打算跟你说了
I've been meaning to talk to you
你退休以后我的角色要扩展
about expanding my role when you retire.
你没打算把我从自己的生意上赶走
You wouldn't squeeze me out of my own operation?
趴下
Get down!
强尼运气真好  刚走就出事儿
Lucky for John he left when he did, huh?
在想什么
What's on your mind?
我想金盆洗手
I want out.
你在撒谎呢吧
I think you're lying to me.
你胆子好大
That's a hell of a thing to say.
证明你不是
Prove you're not.
我等着呢
I'm waiting.
我叫伊诺克
Me llamo Enoch. -
美国人
De los Estados Unidos
我是个疲惫的商人
soy hombre de negocios cansado.
你是个疲惫的商人
You're a tired businessman?
我说成那个了吗  我是想说洗手不干
Is that what I said? I meant retired.
[西语]
Otra almohada debajo de los tobillos, carino.
-[西语]  -我认输了
- Y apurate. - I give up.
再给我脚脖子下垫块枕头  亲爱的
Another pillow under my ankles, honey.
快点的
And make it quick.
我就让你说吧
I think I'll let you do the talking down there.
你打算整天做什么
What do you plan to do all day?
过了今天  我再不做计划了
After today I'm not making plans.
那你今天是什么计划
What's your plan today?
最后一件需要做的事
The last business I need to do.
安安静静地坐着其实也没什么好的
You know, sitting around quietly isn't all it's cracked up to be.
努基
Nuck.
-什么  -我说安安静静地...
- What? - I said, sitting by yourself--
-我在打电话呢  该死  -我也是啊
- I'm on the phone, God damn it. - So am I, Sparky.
抱歉  但是
I'm sorry, it's just that...
喂喂  生意人呢
Hola, Senor Negocios.
我也喜欢沉默寡言的人
Look, I like a man of few words, but--
我再打给你
Let me call you back.
趴在地板上
Facedown on the floor.
朝琪  我到处找你来着
Chalky, I-- I looked all over for you.
你找到我了
You find me.
-不管你是怎么想的  -扯上淡了
- Whatever you think-- - Here it come now.
-我根本...  -谁坐在我的俱乐部里
- I had nothing-- - Who sitting in my club?
-你得理解  -回答我
- You have to understand-- - Answer the question.
纳西斯
Narcisse.
你跟谁做了交易
And who you cutting deals with?
说啊
Say it.
纳西斯
Narcisse.
现在他是供你使唤的黑鬼喽
So he your nigger now, that right?
不是的
Not right.
那你是供他使唤的黑鬼喽
So you his nigger.
这样倒是更好
I think I like that better.
不是你想的那样  我想阻止他来着
It's not what you think. I tried to stop it.
我不知道
I didn't know--
我不想听你
What I don't want to hear from you--
瞎说
words.
昨晚  在我家外面
Outside my house last night,
我家人就在里面  我却不能进去
family inside and I can't even go in.
我穿着别人的衣服
Wearing another man's clothes.
在这儿跟我的朋友站在一起
Standing here with my friend.
你得相信我
You have to trust me.
-我保证  -我不用听你的
-I promise--  - I don't have to do nothing you ask,
无论是做什么  还是去哪
nohow, nowhere.
那你想要什么
Then what is it you want?
纳西斯
Narcisse.
你得相信我  朝琪
You've got to believe me, Chalky.
我也想要他
We want the same thing.
我知道你现在是这么想的
Oh, I know you want it now.
你的常规队员再加八位探员
Your regular team plus eight additional agents?
华盛顿特区
-这些人很危险  -有几个人
- These men are dangerous. - How many are there?
四个  包括汤普森
Four, counting Thompson.
每人都有武装保镖  可能不止一人
Each with an armed guard, most likely more than one.
你真的做到了
You've actually pulled this off?
你好像很惊讶  埃德加
You seem surprised, Edgar.
有组织犯罪
Organized crime?
我这只是正常的怀疑
I'm merely exhibiting a healthy skepticism.
是吗
Is that what it is?
你什么意思
What are you implying?
自从法学院的第一周
That ever since the first week of law school,
你就期望着我会失败
you've been rooting for me to fail.
长官
Sir.
检察官来了
The US Attorney has arrived.
马库斯·贾维
Marcus Garvey.
本月内他们就会对他的上诉给出裁决
They're ruling on his appeal within the month.
恭喜  埃德加
Congratulations, Edgar.
还不用急着庆祝
Well, we're not popping the corks just yet.
再加八名探员
Eight additional agents.
吉姆
Say, Jim.
我觉得
I think it's time,
鉴于我的职位所应得的尊重
considering the respect the position deserves,
你应该开始叫我胡佛局长了
you begin referring to me as Director Hoover.
当你听到求救声时
And when you heard these cries for help,
你做了什么
what did you do?
我下去
I went down--
抱歉  先生  您得大声点
I'm sorry, sir, I do need you to speak up.
我从大厅下去
I went down the hall
去了浴室
into the bathroom.
你是何时认为
And at what time did you form the opinion
那具尸体不是詹姆斯·达莫迪的
that the body was not that of James Darmody?
不是认为
Not an opinion.
你说什么
I beg your pardon?
不是认为
It was not an opinion.
我曾跟他并肩作战
I fought beside him.
这种事是忘不掉的
You don't forget that.
永远忘不掉
Ever.
谢谢  哈罗先生  没有其他问题了
Thank you, Mr. Harrow. No further questions.
我
I, uh...
请求法庭原谅
begging the pardon of the court,
我昨晚才收到案件细节
I only received the particulars of this case last--
我注意到你戴了眼镜
I notice you're wearing glasses,
哈罗德...哈罗先生
Mr. Harold-- Harrow.
是装饰用的吗
Are they for cosmetic purposes?
什么
What?
你戴眼镜是为了好看  还是真的需要
Are they for reasons of vanity or do you need them to see?
眼镜能...
They keep...
法官大人  如果证人含糊不清  听证会还...
Your Honor, what's the point of a hearing if the witness--
先生  请你尽可能地大声讲话
Sir, I remind you to speak as loudly as you're able.
眼镜能抵住面具
They keep my face on.
好的
Yes, all right.
那么我们能相信
So are we to believe
你的那只好眼的眼力
that the vision of your remaining eye...
法官大人  骚扰证人
Badgering, Your Honor.
比达莫迪先生亲生母亲的眼睛更好使吗
...is more reliable than that of Mr. Darmody's own mother?
我知道是怎么回事
I know what happened.
我知道我看到了什么
I know what I saw.
我知道
I know.
法官大人  已经颁发了一张有效的死亡证明
Your Honor, a duly certified death record has already--
是动过手脚的死亡证明  法官大人
A jerry-rigged death record, Your Honor.
而且我的委托人
And surely my client's veracity
-在辨认自己孩子这事上...  -根本没有尸体
- as to the identity of her own child... - There's no body.
我们说的正是这件事
The exact point that we're debating.
...应该更重视
...should carry more weight...
-没有别人  -丧子之痛...
- There's no body.  -the grief of this aggrieved-- bereaved--
-我方有供词  -没有尸体
- We have a confession. - There's no body.
为了您自己的辩护  我必须坚持
I have to insist for your own defense,
-拜托...  -没有尸体
- please-- - There's no body.
德里克先生  请你的代理人冷静  不然我会将她逐出法庭
Mr. Drake, keep your client in check or I'll have her removed.
那是我儿子  我之前说过什么都不重要
It was my son. It doesn't matter what I said.
没有别人
There's no one there.
我在恋爱  我受了欺骗
I was in love. I was tricked.
这哪有天理
How can that be right?
你好  打扰一下
Hello. Excuse me!
不许我说话  不许我活
I'm not allowed to speak. I'm not allowed to live.
快接线
Get on the wire.
凭什么男人想干什么就能干什么
Why does a man get to do anything he wants?
巾帼英雄
That a girl!
她疯了  尸体在哪里
She's off! Where's the body? -
重点是让他们开口
The idea is to get them talking--
贩酒  海洛因  随便你知道的
alcohol importation, heroin, what have you.
或许他们有所谋划  或许是抢劫
Maybe they're planning something, a heist perhaps.
互相勾结
Conspiring with one another.
我们在这边  伊莱
We're over here, Eli.
塞尔比探员和我们其他同事
Agent Selby and our other operatives
会在隔壁听着
will be stationed in the next room listening in.
你听到留声机响起来  就是信号
When you hear the radio go on, that's your signal.
什么信号
My signal for what?
你离开去洗手间
To excuse yourself, go to the washroom.
事情会很棘手
Things could get a little messy.
你要做的就是保持冷静
All you have to do is remain calm.
努基和其他人都不会知道你有参与
Neither Nucky nor the others will ever know you were involved.
你有兄弟吗  诺克斯
You have a brother, Knox?
或者你  管你他妈的叫什么
Or whatever the fuck your name is.
-有亲人吗  -不关你事
- A family? - That's none of your business.
操你
Fuck you.
还有你  你这自以为是的兔崽子
And you, too, you smug son of a bitch.
我有个兄弟  名叫克劳德
I have a brother named Claude.
在华盛顿海事法庭做律师
He's an admiralty lawyer in Washington.
-你害过克劳德吗  -他不是罪犯  伊莱
- You ever fuck Claude over? - He's not a criminal, Eli.
而且你这样做是为了你儿子
And you're doing this for your son.
我需要一份保证
I need a guarantee.
-没有什么保证  -我没跟你说话
- There are no guaran-- - I'm not talking to you.
这事办成  我儿子不牵扯进去
We pull this off, my son stays out of it.
所有那些破事  关于他的谣言
All that other shit, this malarkey with him
还有那个室友  一笔勾销
and the roommate, that all goes away.
我们都有各自的风险
We both have a lot riding on--
我才不信这句鬼话
I don't even think it's true, by the way.
把他们弄到这里
Get them in this room,
你哥哥  马赫里亚  还有其他人
your brother, Masseria and the others,
威尔就没什么可担心的了
and Will has nothing to worry about.
威尔
Will?
帮我个忙
Do me a favor.
别说的好像你跟他很熟一样
Stop talking like you know him.
我说这搞什么呢
I mean, the balls, right?
一路送到西塞罗
Took them all the way to Cicero,
街对面的楼里
building right across the street.
他们必须知道你在这里  阿尔
They had to know you were here, Al.
提前知道
In advance.
那电话
The phone call.
他们怎么知道的号码
Now, how did he get the number anyway?
芝加哥
那个叫海米·魏斯的犹太鬼
That Jew prick Hymie Weiss.
其实他是天主教徒
Actually, he's Catholic.
沃贾霍夫斯基
Wojciechoski.
沃贾什么
Wo-ja-what?
他的姓  他改姓叫魏斯
His name. He changed it to Weiss.
坐
Sit down.
喝酒
Have a drink.
我不喝酒  先生
I don't drink, sir.
那现在开始喝
Then start.
那枪击是不是魏斯搞的
So was it Weiss that done the shooting or not?
如你所说  不管是谁
As you said, whoever it was
他都嚣张到把手伸进你地盘了
felt comfortable enough to venture into your territory.
这是干嘛
What's this?
董事会吗
A board meeting?
在说枪击的事
Talking about the shooting.
感谢老天造了百叶窗
Thank God for them shutters.
约翰  你怎么看
So what do you think, John?
魏斯  巴格斯·莫兰还有那家伙
Weiss with Bugs Moran and the other one...
阴谋家德鲁齐
Schemer Drucci.
-你这样想  -当然
- You think so? - Sure.
奥巴尼恩那事之后  还会有谁
After the O'Banion thing, who else could it be?
当然你是对的
Yeah, I'm sure you're right.
好了吉米  把这鬼东西弄走
All right, Jimmy, get this thing the fuck out of here.
你烦死我了  快点
You're killing me. Come on.
你别问我先说  很薄
Before you ask, it's light.
我已经知道了
I already know that.
现在这情况  你那个朋友  什么博士
This whole situation, your friend there, the doctor.
纳西斯
Narcisse.
反正绝对没有让事情简单起来
It ain't making things easier, that's for sure.
五车威士忌被城北退回来了
Five trucks full of scotch turned away from the Northside.
他一定是从纽约运酒过来
I mean, he must be getting his liquor trucked down from New York.
综上各种原因你的信封才薄了
All of which answers the question why the envelope is short.
我说我已经知道了  米奇
I said I already know, Mickey.
好吧  我只是觉得你应该听到解释
All right. I just thought you deserved an explanation.
你计划怎么办
So what's the plan?
关于什么
With what?
那个念圣经的黑鬼
This Bible-thumping coon.
昔日交际花拒认罪行"那是我儿子"
我们还要忍他多久
I mean, how much more of his bullshit are we gonna take?
这事有人管  伊莱
It's being handled, Eli.
-怎么管  -我不知道
- How? - I don't know.
朝琪没有消息吗
And nothing from Chalky?
会面  都准备好了吗
The meeting. Are we set?
明晚  在布伦海姆
Tomorrow night, the Blenheim.
马赫里亚  兰斯基和佩德鲁塞利
Masseria, Lansky, and Petrucelli.
要确保他们...
Make sure they--
汤普森先生
Mr. Thompson.
我去玛瑙俱乐部找过您
I looked for you in the Onyx Club.
那如今对我来说可不算安全
Not the safest place for me these days.
我需要您帮我一个忙
I need to ask you a favor.
我已经给了你一份工作  哈罗先生
I already gave you a job, Mr. Harrow.
让我们单独谈谈
Give us a minute.
吉米·达莫迪
Jimmy Darmody.
他怎么了
What about him?
我需要知道他在哪里
I need to know where he is.
他已经火化了
He was cremated
注射毒品过量死在他母亲的浴缸里
after overdosing in his mother's tub.
你我都知道那不是真的
You and I both know that isn't true.
我也是读了报纸才知道
I only know what I read in the papers.
那么你读到吉莉安·达莫迪
Then you've read Gillian Darmody
因谋杀被逮捕的消息了
has been arrested for murder.
可那是荒唐之言
But that's ludicrous.
死在浴缸里的是詹姆斯
It was James who died in that tub.
如果法庭相信了
If they believe that,
她就自由了
she'll go free.
她肯定要来和我争孩子
And she'll come back for the boy to spite me.
经历了那么多磨难
After all of this,
我和我妻子
my wife and I...
是承受不起的
could not bear that.
假如有个匿名线人
If somehow an anonymous source
向官方透露吉米尸体的位置
were to disclose to the authorities
你愿意为这个线人
the whereabouts of Jimmy's body...
做些什么吗
what would you do for that anonymous source?
你要我做什么都行
I would do whatever you asked.
-别挤  各位  -好了好了
- Nice and orderly, guys. - All right, all right.
给医生让路
Let the doctor through.
各位后退一下  讲究点风度
Stand back, boys. A little dignity.
-拍张照片  -回来
- Get a picture. - Come on, get back.
-别推人  -是达莫迪吗
- Hey, don't push. - Is it Darmody?
右腿六根钢钉
Six screws in the right femur.
-是达莫迪  -各位  请后退
- It's him. It's Darmody. - Fellas, please, stand back.
这是达莫迪  那么那个是谁
If that's Darmody, then who's the other one?
拿回来
Hey, get it back!
放松点
Take it easy!
下午版有内容了
Call it in for the afternoon edition.
那我先来
Well, guess I'll kick things off and--
-艾德  -怎么了
- Ed. - Yeah, Nuck?
滚出去
Get the fuck out of here.
这是我办公室啊
It's my office.
别逼我把你拉下来
I'll change that if it's the last thing I do.
我只是做了该做的
I just did what I had to.
你肯定
You of all people--
您最好让我们独处一会
It would be best to leave us be.
-你见过他  -我可没说
- You've seen him. - I didn't say that.
你有他的消息
You've heard from him.
反正不是有就是没有
Either you have or you have not.
要是没有  那就是浪费
If you have not, then my time--
他要了结这一切
He wants this to end.
他不早就找我了结吗
Endings have been attempted, have they not?
-各方面都是  -这关系到他家人
- On all sides. - This is a question of family.
女儿要结婚了  他得出席
His daughter's getting married. He wants to be there.
他想全身而退
He's looking for safe passage in and out.
拿什么交换
In exchange for what?
我就是个牵线的
I'm just the middleman here.
你们不是朋友吗
I thought you were friends.
我没有朋友  只有合作伙伴
I don't have friends. I have partners.
你救过他一命
You tried to save his life.
有回报我才伸手  他现在什么都没有
I bet on a horse to win. He didn't even place.
世道已经变了
Today is a different day.
那你以后要向谁伸手呢
On whom will you wager tomorrow?
我就明说了吧
Let's get something straight, all right?
你的信仰  你过去的悲剧
Your beliefs, your tragic history,
我他妈才懒得听呢
I don't give a rat's ass about any of it.
我们两个人种唯一的共同点
The only thing your people and mine have in common--
就是都认钱
we both know what a dollar's worth.
这里没钱就去那里挣
And if we can't make it one way, we'll make it another.
这座城市是我的蛋糕
I have a lot at stake in this town.
你要是想分一块吃  就等着瞧吧
Try to take it from me, we have a problem.
俱乐部  北城
The club, the Northside,
哪个黑人管都一样
I don't care which of you coloreds runs them,
给我管好就行
as long as they're run.
至于分成  还有你的市长小伙伴
The percentage, your new pal the mayor,
我们回头再说
we'll discuss those later.
这事必须了结掉
This just needs to be over.
怎么了结
Over how?
你们两个谈
That's for you to arrange.
请你解释一下
I urge you to be explicit.
我不希望以后再有人
I don't ever want to worry about that spook
暗地里盯着我
coming at me in the dark again.
明白了吗
Do we understand each other?
明白了
We do.
终于
At long last.
我去找朝琪安排你俩谈谈
Then I'll let Chalky know you're willing to talk.
他要我告诉你件事
Something he wanted me to tell you.
说你肯定感兴趣
Said you'd be interested.
什么
Yes?
那个歌手
That singer.
他说知道她在哪
He says he knows where she is.
买点洋蓟
And be sure to pick up the artichokes.
二十二美分一磅
They're 22 cents a pound.
-那又怎么样  等等  -我可不买
- So? Aspetta. - I'm not paying that.
咱又不是要饭的  洋蓟还买不起
What, are we paupers? I want artichokes, for God's sake.
他妈的
Maladetta funga.
我刚喷过水
I just sprayed all this.
再来  正常讲话
Go ahead. Speak in a normal tone.
测试  测试  阿尔法  贝塔  伽马
Test, test. Alpha, beta, gamma.
测试  测试
Test, test.
周一二三四五
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday.
测试  一  二
Test, test. One, two.
一二三四五
One, two, three, four, five.
测试  测试
Panama. Test, test.
在海的那边山的那边
On the shores of Gitche Gumee, on the shining...
大厅安排四个人  两端各两个
I want four agents in the lobby, two at either end of the hall.
好像有点多吧
That seems excessive.
我管它好像什么呢
I didn't ask how it seems.
弹夹再检查一遍
Check those magazines, gentlemen.
子弹有限
We can't afford any misfires.
怎么样
Well?
-长官  -听不听得见
- Sir? - Can you hear him or not?
-基本都听见了  -什么叫基本上
- For the most part. - What does that mean?
-我基本都能  -听不听得见
- I can make out most-- - Yes or no?
放松  吉姆  没事的
Relax, Jim. It'll be all right.
这是我的事业  哈罗德
This is only my career, Harold.
事情办好了我才能放松
I'll relax when it's over.
好吧
Right.
好的
Yes.
怀特先生回去的
Mr. White will be there.
纳西斯的人  他们九点到俱乐部
Narcisse's man, he'll be at the club by 9:00.
爸爸
Pop.
爸爸  是努基伯父
Pop, it's Uncle Nucky.
小点声
Cut the racket, huh?
喂
Hello?
那个会  你来接我吧
The meeting, I want you to pick me up.
我们一起过去
We'll drive over together.
直接在那见面多好
Easier just to meet there, no?
应该一起进去  兄弟齐心嘛
We should walk in together, present a united front.
反正也顺路
I'm on your way anyway.
没问题
Sure thing.
一会见
I'll see you in a little while.
努基伯父吗
That Uncle Nucky?
什么  是啊
What? Yeah.
-他什么事  -什么事
- What'd he want? - What'd he want?
关你什么事
How's that your concern?
不是  我只是
It's not. I just--
我很好奇  仅此而已
I'm curious, that's all.
跟你母亲说我晚点回来
Tell your mother I'll be late.
通往候车大厅
从卡姆登开往费城的火车开始检票
All aboard the Camden Line for Philadelphia.
转乘北岸路线
Connecting with the North Shore Line...
两张卧铺  和餐车用餐票
Two sleepers with extra vouchers for the dining car.
汤米和我睡一张床
Tommy and I can double up.
你的姐夫  这个休伯特
Your brother-in-law, this Hubert,
他知道你要去吗
he got the message?
他会提前九十分钟到
He'll be there 90 minutes early.
记得要数数你看见了几头牛
Hey, make sure you count how many cows you see.
-向我汇报  -好的
- I want a full report. - Okay.
汤米
Tommy.
我爱你
I love you.
来吧  伙计  我们买点软糖路上吃
Come on, sport. Let's get some Chuckles for the road.
怎么回事  在告别吗
What was that? Good-bye?
-不是  -跟我保证你会来
- No. - Promise me you're coming.
因为我从未没见过你姐姐
Because I've never even spoken to your sister
如果你不来的话就太尴尬了
and it will be pretty goddamn awkward if you don't show--
我们三天以后见
I will see you in three days.
要不然我就去找你  把你抓到威斯康辛州
Or I will hunt you down and drag you to Wisconsin.
我保证
I promise.
有人吗
Hello?
努基
Nuck?
在伤到人之前把那东西收起来
Put that away before someone gets hurt.
怎么他妈回事  人都在哪
The fuck's going on? Where is everyone?
-关门了  -为什么
- Closing the place up. - What for?
能不能把那东西收起来
Would you put that away, please?
我要走了
I'm leaving town.
跟萨利去古巴
Heading to Cuba with Sally.
什么时候
When?
我办完事情就走
As soon as I finish what I need to do.
你打算什么时候告诉我
When were you gonna tell me?
我打算现在告诉你
I intended to tell you now.
我们还要开会
We have a meeting.
-马赫里亚  -没有会议
- Masseria is-- - There is no meeting.
我知道是怎么回事了
I saw to that.
旅店登记了三个空房间
There are names on a hotel register with three empty rooms.
还有你和我
And you and me.
-努基  我  -努基  我什么
- Nucky, I-- - Nucky, I what?
努基  我犯错了
Nucky, I made a mistake?
努基  对不起
Nucky, I'm sorry?
我说什么有什么关系
What's it matter what I say?
你能失去的东西很多
You have a lot to lose.
我吗  我一无所有
Me? I don't have anything.
早晚你都会夺走
Sooner or later you wind up taking it all.
我无能为力
Can't help it.
我准备好了
I'm ready.
你呢
Are you?
是你罪有应得
It's what you deserve.
-爸  -走开
- Pop! - Back off!
-那是我儿子  -你在干什么
- That's my son! - What are you doing?
-他要杀了你  -不  不会
- He's gonna kill you.  - No, he's not.
他不会  他不会
He's-- he's not.
你跟他说
You tell him.
告诉他怎么回事
Tell him what's going on.
诺克斯
Knox.
你是对的  他不是禁酒探员
You had it right. He's no Prohee.
你那个同学  那个谋杀指控
The kid at school, that murder charge
你把检察官买通了  他知道了
you had the DA squash, he knows.
他知道
He knows.
他想要你  纽约和佛罗里达的人
He wants you and New York and Florida
坐在一起
all together all at once.
这是不让他
That's the price
进监狱的代价
to keep him out of jail.
- 爸  我  -你向着他
- Pop, I-- - So you go to him?
胳膊肘向外拐
Over your father?
我能收拾残局
I'm the one who can fix it.
他本来应该有所成就
He was supposed to amount to something.
他还是会的
He's still going to.
什么成就  成为一个在旅店里
What? A man in an empty hotel
拿枪指着他兄弟的男人
pointing a gun at his brother?
我是为了家人
I did it for the family.
你没有家人
You don't have a family.
我有
I do.
现在你也想拥有
Now you want that, too.
什么都无法填补你内心的空洞
Nothing will fill that hole you got inside.
你还不知道吗
Don't you know that yet?
这是你搞砸的  伊莱
This is your mess, Eli.
自己受着吧
Drown in it.
他们不会来了
They're not coming.
你说不准
You don't know that.
你被骗了  吉姆  直面现实吧
You've been duped, Jim. Let's face it.
你可高兴了  是吧
You'd love that, wouldn't you?
-什么  -能让你这一天很愉快吧
- What? - That would make your entire day.
让我们单独待一会儿  好吗
Give us a minute, will you?
你很生气  我理解
You're upset. I understand.
生气
Upset?
-生气  -冷静点
- Upset?! - Just calm down.
你以为我不知道吗  你  胡佛还有其他人
You think I don't know? You, Hoover and the others,
-这是个多大的笑话啊  -吉姆  我
- what a joke this has all been? - Jim, I--
你从未支持我  从来没有
You were never on board, never for a second.
我赌上了所有
I have put everything on the line!
我觉得你应该把你的枪给我
I think you should give me your sidearm.
什么
What?
你现在情绪不稳定
You are not keeping on an even keel.
你想要我的枪  哈罗德
You want my gun, Harold?
来拿啊
Why don't you take it?
他要见你
He's asking for you.
你醒着吗
You awake?
感觉怎么样
How you feeling?
我很好
I'm okay.
以前从未听你这样说过
I've never heard you say that before.
是吗啡的关系
Morphine.
放松好好享受吧
Well, relax and enjoy it.
我们有二十四小时的保镖和护士
We got round-the-clock guards, nurses, too.
你很快就会出院了
You'll be out of here in no time.
然后我们就会弄死那帮狗娘养的
And then we'll get them sons of bitches.
这是年轻人的游戏
This is a young man's game.
我不参与
I'm not gonna fight.
你想放走他们
You're gonna let them get away with it?
是你的  阿尔
It's yours, Al.
-拿着  -什么  拿什么
- Take it. - What? Take what?
整个组织
The whole operation.
天呐  强尼  你确定吗
Jesus, Johnny. Are you sure?
你赢了  孩子
You win, kid.
我不挡你路
I'm out of your way.
我该去欧洲养老了
It's Europe for me.
-怎么回事  -威尔呢
- What is going on? - Where's Will?
-伊莱  -他在这里
- Eli... - Is he here or not?
你得对我说实话
You need to be honest with me.
伊莱  你忘了我们有约吗
Eli. Did you forget we had an appointment?
没忘
No.
等我会儿
Give me a second.
-我得和这位先生聊会儿  -没错夫人
- I need to speak with this man. - He does, ma'am.
-我必须  -威利在哪里
- Please, I need-- - Where is Willie?
问得好
That's an excellent question, actually.
-妈妈  安在哭  -马上
- Mom, Anne is crying. - Just one second.
-去楼上  -伊莱
- Go back upstairs. - Eli.
谁能告诉我出了什么事
Will someone please tell me what is going on?
该死的  上楼去
Now, God damn it. Go upstairs.
我哥哥知道了...
Look, my brother knows--
我之前告诉你会发生什么事儿  伊莱
What did I tell you would happen, Eli?
-能不能听我说  -我不想听了
- Will you just hear me out? - I'm through talking.
-我在向你解释  -你的儿子要去坐牢了
- I'm trying to explain to you. - Your son is going to jail.
之前有个男孩
There was this boy a while back.
叫埃利斯啥
Ellis something.
和你儿子同龄
About your own son's age.
是真的童子军
A real Boy Scout type.
他偷车的时候被我抓了
I arrested him on a stolen vehicles charge.
他被判关在联邦监狱四年
He got four years in the federal lockup.
我最近听到的消息
Last I heard,
他很受狱友的欢迎
he was very popular with the other inmates.
我要杀了你  你个混
I will fucking kill you, you son of a--
你是在威胁一名联邦探员吗
Are you threatening a federal agent?
把手腕给我
Give me your wrist.
我的搭档  塞尔比探员  他觉得我疯了
My partner, Agent Selby, he thinks I'm crazy.
你觉得我疯了吗  伊莱
Do you think I'm crazy, Eli?
没事  你可以说
It's okay, you can say it.
我不知道你是个什么样的人
I don't know what you are.
我来告诉你
I'll tell you what I am.
我是那个
I'm the man who's gonna--
杀了你
Fucking kill you!
妈妈
Mama!
伊莱  伊莱
Eli! Eli!
我的天
Oh, my God!
别下来  我马上来
Stay up there! I'm coming up.
爸爸  爸爸
Dad! Dad!
爸爸   爸爸
Dad! Daddy!
我的儿子
My son!
My fucking son!
我们做什么
What you want us to do?
好好待着  别大惊小怪
Stay right here and don't raise no fuss.
不喜欢
Don't like it.
也没打算让人喜欢
Ain't meant to be liked.
告诉我你的条件
Tell me your terms.
你啥都不缺
You get everything.
-我已经有了  -那我们还谈什么
- I already have that. - Then why we talking?
我想要  你也想要
I want and you want.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
埃及有法老
Egypt had its pharaohs
国王从罗马
and the emperors ruled from Rome...
她在哪里
Where is she?
你不在的地方
Where she is and you ain't.
你女儿的婚礼  没有问题
Your daughter's wedding. Safe passage.
很好
That right.
-然后呢  -只要我走了  你还担心什么
- Then what? - Matter to you so long as I'm gone?
女儿换女儿
A daughter for a daughter.
那女的不是你女儿
That woman ain't your blood.
你怎么可能理解
How could you possibly understand?
我知道我讨她的欢心
I understand I rock her fine.
轻而易举的事
That was some sweet jelly.
现在她老摆脸色
Now her face ain't right
我不再需要看她的脸色了
and I don't need to be looking at that no more.
看看高贵的野蛮人
Behold the noble savage.
就是我
That me.
一边口袋揣钞票  一边揣枪
Bankroll in the one pocket, pistol in the other.
其余的
And all the rest...
关我屁事
I never did give a fuck.
了解彼此了吧
We see each other now?
你知道汤普森先生让我做什么吧
You know what your friend Mr.Thompson asked me to do?
做了我
Kick a bullet in my head.
不过不会在这里做
But that ain't gonna happen here.
我们是文明人
We civilized.
你们都走不出巷子
None of you will make it past the alley.
那你就别想见到她了
Then you ain't never gonna see her again.
你从想掐死她的母亲手里救下来的孩子
Baby you save from that half and half choke her mama.
那个男人被抓到了吗
They ever catch that man?
告诉我她在哪里
Tell me where she is.
我女儿的婚礼
My girl wedding.
没有婚礼
There is no wedding.
你知道什么
What you know about it?
梅布尔告诉我的
I know what Maybelle told me.
你听她亲口给你说吧
But hear it from her yourself.
我一声令下  她就没命了
A nod from me and she's gone.
我们算扯平了
I'd say that makes us even.
♪我希望可以和妹妹凯特一样摆动♪
♪Oh, I wish that I could shimmy like my sister Kate♪
♪像盘子上的果冻一样摆动♪
♪Shimmy like the jelly on the plate♪
♪我妈妈昨晚想知道♪
♪My mama wanted to know last night♪
♪为什么男生都觉得凯特很好♪
♪Says, "Why the boys think Kate's so nice?♪
告诉我
Tell me!
♪知道她会摆动  大家都知道♪
Knows she can shimmy and it's undertood
♪我知道已经晚了  但我会赶上♪
I know it's late, but I'll be up to date
♪当我像妹妹凯特一样摆动♪
When I shimmy like my sister Kate
♪像我妹妹凯特一样摆动♪
Oh, yeah, shimmy like my sister Kate
告诉我
Tell me.
梅布尔  亲爱的
Maybelle, baby?
乖女儿
Baby girl.
他在上面
He's up there!
-快走  提米  -梅布尔
- Let's go, Timmy! - Maybelle?
-我们快走  -我不会丢下她
- We got to go. - I ain't leaving her.
我们得马上走  快走
We got to leave here now. Come on, let's go!
-快走  -梅布尔  梅布尔
- We got to go! - Maybelle! Maybelle! God, my baby!
都不准动  我们是调查局的
Nobody move. Bureau of Investigation.
我们正在找伊莱·汤普森
We're looking for Eli Thompson.
走走走
Go, go, go.
走
Go!
走走走
Go. Go on, go.
-停  现在怎么办  -我不知道
- Stop! Now what? -  I don't know!
我不知道去哪儿
I don't know where to go.
我们该怎么办
- What are we supposed to do?
大家都从前门跑了
- Everybody's gone and run out the front door.
-让让  各位  -我们走
- Out of the way, folks. - Let's go, people.
-快点  各位  -快点
- Move it, fellas. - Scoot back.
好  这边
Okay, over here.
抱歉
Excuse me.
退后退后
Back, back, back.
-退后  -让开
- Back. - Hey, get off.
让我们过去
Let us through!
把他们带走
Yeah, take them away!
伊诺克·汤普森
Enoch Thompson?
是我
Yes?
先生  请跟我走
I need you to come with me, sir.
-我被逮捕了吗  -不跟我走你就要被逮捕了
- Am I under arrest? - You will be if you don't comply.
你想要什么  警官
What is it you want, Officer?
你弟弟的下落
The whereabouts of your brother.
你要指控他取消会面吗
Are you going to charge him with cancelling a meeting?
不  是谋杀联邦探员
No, with the murder of a federal agent.
你们在一八九八年的新奥尔良港口
You entered this country through the Port of New Orleans
进入这个国家  没错吧
in 1898, is that correct?
你说什么
I beg your pardon?
没错吧
Is that correct?
你是谁
Who are you?
问问题的人
The one asking questions.
一八九八  没错
1898, yes.
在美国待了二十六年
26 years in the United States...
却仍然不是公民
but you're not a citizen.
这是作为拘禁我的理由吗
And that is grounds for detaining me how?
你为什么要待在一个
Why would you go on living in a country
你不想成为其人民的国家中
you don't wish to belong to?
被流放者没法选择他的故乡
The exile does not choose his Babylon.
你的同胞  贾维
Your, um, compatriot Garvey.
他认为你们都应该回到非洲去
He thinks you should all return to Africa.
这是对他的哲学的过度解读
That would be an oversimplification of his philosophy.
我理解错哪里了
What am I missing?
我怕你理解不了
I doubt that I could make you to understand.
你看上去挺聪明
You seem to be a clever fellow.
你觉得是谁来决定真理的内容
Who do you think gets to decide what the truth is?
真理就是那些掌握权力的人想让它们成为的样子
Truth is what those in power wish it to be.
在调查期间
During the course of investigating
因为马科斯·贾维的煽动性活动
the seditious activities of Marcus Garvey,
詹姆斯·M·托利弗
James M. Tolliver,
调查局特别探员
a special agent with the Bureau of Investigation,
被一名不明身份的黑人男性
was murdered in Atlantic City, New Jersey,
谋杀在新泽西州大西洋城
by an unidentified colored male.
瓦伦丁·纳西斯博士帮助调查局
Dr. Valentin Narcisse assisted the Bureau
逮捕了嫌疑犯
in apprehending the suspect.
他进一步承认了和胡佛局长
He further agreed in a private conversation
进行了私人交谈
with Director Hoover to provide
同意提供更多关于贾维先生
ongoing secret intelligence regarding Mr. Garvey
的激进运动及其同国外组织联系的
with particular concern to his radical agenda
相关情报
and his ties to foreign powers.
他为什么要这么做
Why would he do that?
来展示出他
To demonstrate his commitment
对这片接纳他的土地的忠诚
to the values of his adopted land.
贾维兄弟是位
Brother Garvey is a hero
致力于自由的英雄
devoted to the liberation of a great people.
但你不是
But you are not.
你只是个无足轻重的小人物
You are just a peddler and a pimp
乖乖坐在监狱里
sitting in a jail cell.
我是个商人  也是个基督徒
I am a businessman and a follower of Christ.
你同意跟我们合作  你愿意当什么
You agree to cooperate, you can go on pretending
就继续当什么
to be anything you want.
不合作  我可以向你保证
You don't, and I will make sure
你再也见不到美利坚的阳光了
you never see daylight in America again.
我听不见
I cannot hear you.
我说  是
I said yes.
是  什么
Yes, what?
是
Yes...
先生
sir.
老妈要的一切都在这了
That's everything Ma asked for.
汤姆随后会去船上
Tom can run it up to Brigantine later.
除非你想去
Unless you want to do it.
我要在城里呆一会
I'm gonna stay in town for a little.
-不是想给你说教  -努基伯父  能不能
- Not trying to tell you-- - Uncle Nucky, can we just--
但是他们都靠你了
But they're counting on you--
你的母亲  兄弟  姊妹
your mother, brothers and sisters.
你现在说了算
You're in charge now.
明白吗
You understand?
我今晚出发
I'll drive up tonight.
这是正确的决定
That's the right decision.
我要怎么告诉他
What am I supposed to tell them?
说你父亲和朋友待在西部  很安全
That your father is safe with friends out west.
他们不知道具体地址最好
It's best they don't know where.
这对大家来说都很艰难  但也只能这样
It's hard on everyone, but that's how it has to be.
真的吗
Is he?
什么真的吗
Is he what?
他很安全
Safe.
说出你的想法  威尔
Speak your mind, Will.
如果我没出现  你会怎么做
If I hadn't shown up, what would you have done?
他是你的父亲  我的弟弟
He's your father, my brother.
我没有你想的心那么狠
And I'm not the person you think I am.
晚点来信天翁
Come by the Albatross later.
我们一起走
We'll both head up.
这样我们就能待在一起了
That way, all of us can be together, all right?
会越来越容易接受的  等着看吧
It gets easier. You'll see.